

## **Enrique Marín** Web Dev & Designer La Paz, BCS, México

enriquemarin.xyz

#### Contact

**1** +52 (612) 104 9341

➡ enrique.marin.h@hotmail.com

in /enriquemarin

#### About me

I am a young developer enthusiastic about innovative and technological projects that seek to impact people's lives.

In recent years I have worked in areas such as web development and mobile Apps, as well as graphic creation projects such as branding and digital marketing.

#### **Skills**

## Present

HTML, JavaScript, SCSS, Vue, Nuxt, Node.js, Adonis, MongoDB, MySQL.

## ☐ Design

UI Design & Kits, Branding, Prototyping, Responsive Web design.

#### Tools & Services

Visual Studio Code, Github, Heroku, Strapi, DigitalOcean, AWS, Cloudinary, Figma, Adobe Xd, Illustrator, Photoshop.

### Languages

**English** intermediate (B2) Spanish Native

#### Some projects



#### Tresam Capital

Professional Website made it when I worked on Applab.mx

tresamcapital.com



## Capbook

Dashboard created to set a base grid template for my projects

capbook.vercel.app



### Travel

Responsive website exercise only with HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

travel-website-responsive.vercel.app



#### **Hates Map**

Web App to find and register street hotdogs. Open project

hates-map.vercel.app

To see more, check out my Github



# **Experience**



Applab.mx Sep 2021 - Jan 2022 (4 months)

### Front End Web Developer (Remote)

I worked on websites for businesses and clients looking for a more customized design. I also worked on a project in production for a German company called Bits&Birds in which we developed a large platform for the management of vacancies and candidates, working continuously hand in hand with the development team of that company.



Freelance 2020 - 2021

## Brand designer, UI designer & Web Development

Independent professional focused on development services of web systems, brand design, interface design (UI / UX).



**Async Agencia Creativa** 2019 - 2022

## CoFounder, Designer & Web Developer

Async is an agency dedicated to inpulse companies and entrepreneurs into the digital world through branding, marketing and websites.



Relapp 2019 (6 months)

### Brand Designer, UI Designer & App Developer (Flutter)

App sudcalifornian to search all kind of local business and promos in your town. We developed this app with Flutter using Firebase for backend, and we deployed on Google Play Store and App Store.



JastMedia 2018 (2 months)

## Front End Developer, Content Loader

Juniper Data Center's Extending Department Focused on Websites Development for clients in United States.

## Education



Bachelor in Computing Systems 2013-2018 Tecnológico Nacional de México Campus La Paz Security and Web Development speciality

Certifications

You can see the certifications in my LinkedIn profile







